limebooth.com 2010-11-20

# Limebooth ~ About › Legal › Privacy

Limebooth respects the privacy of visitors to its site.  To inform you as clearly as possible about the way in which we collect and use your personal data, we have drawn up a privacy policy that contains all the necessary information.  Please read this policy carefully before you provide information about yourself.

**Account**

To gain access to all our services, you are required to open an account on Limebooth.com.  The account of someone else may not be used without authorisation.  You are consequently responsible for the activity that takes place on your account.  If your account is used without your consent nonetheless, you must inform Limebooth accordingly at once. 

**Personal pages and personal messages**

As a user, you have personal pages with an “information” component and a “portfolio” in which you can share your own music preferences and talents, but can also add a “music _band_ ” or texts, and manage a list of friends.  Only a user with an “ _Artist”_ profile will be able to upload video images too by means of the “ _flash video player_ ” that we provide.  As we strive for quality video contents, the video that you upload must meet a minimum resolution requirement.  All these pages can be viewed also by other visitors to the site.

As a Limebooth user you can send messages to other members via the site.  For instance, you can send a request to an artist.  You are liable for the messages that you exchange with other members.  Limebooth does not intervene in this private communication and consequently cannot be held liable. If a certain member should nonetheless violate the rules of these general terms and conditions by “ _spamming”_ for instance, a complaint can be lodged using the feedback form of the reporting button (abuse@limebooth.com). If this complaint turns out to be justified, Limebooth can issue an initial serious warning to the user in question and proceed to close his or her account where necessary.

**Our policy for minor**

We understand that minors are interested in music too.  If you are underage, we want to ask you to inform your parents before you provide your data (e.g. by completing your profile) to Limebooth.  They are responsible for you and can warn you about the dangers that the Internet may entail.  We advise you to use an alias and to avoid providing overly personal information.  Limebooth may not be held liable if minors use our services without parental supervision.

**Personal data**

For optimal use of the platform, it is necessary for you to create a profile.  When creating your profile, you will be asked to give your name, sex, e-mail address, telephone number, address, a picture of yourself and a password.  In addition, you must also indicate your profile type ( _artist / fan_ ). We give you the possibility to provide other data (such as membership in a possible music band, an extra field for family members, biographical data and your portfolio).

Your e-mail address will not be shown on our site and will not be given to third parties.  The requested data are essential so as to be able to make optimal use of the services that we provide and the user options on the website, as well as to be able to contact you if problems should arise.

When you surf on the site, you provide information which is temporarily collected by us for technical reasons in particular.  Like many sites, we use “cookies” and collect certain information when your browser accesses our site.

Limebooth does not make such data available to third parties on any account, except:

  * If Limebooth is required to do so by law; 
  * If the judicial authorities or police services so request; 
  * If such third parties are called upon by Limebooth so as to be able to provide the services you have requested. 

In the exceptional case where Limebooth intends to pass your personal data on to organisations with which it cooperates, your prior consent will always be requested.

Pursuant to the Privacy Protection Act of 8 December 1992, you have a number of rights concerning your personal data.  The right to inspect entitles you to inspect data that have been collected by the web platform.  The right to correct enables you to improve incomplete or incorrect data.

**Log files**

The web platform also collects information in log files (IP address, browser type).  This information is used for traffic and profile analysis.  In other words, data are here collected on the actions you carry out on our site.

**Links**

Our site contains links to other websites or to other information.  These sites are not under the control of Limebooth.  We are therefore not responsible for their privacy policy or the way in which they deal with your personal data.  We consequently advise you to have a look at the privacy policies of those sites. When placing a link, you must verify yourself whether said link is not to material or information of suspect origin.  If problems arise from a link to illegal material, we will contact the party that placed the link about it and, where necessary, convey our liability to that party.

**Security**

All appropriate security measures are taken to protect your data against, in particular, unexpected destruction, accidental loss, malicious loss or unauthorised access.

**Consent**

It is important for Limebooth that our visitors get a clear picture of the way in which we deal with their personal data.  It is moreover important that you are properly informed when you consent to the processing of your personal data.  If, after reading this privacy policy, you decide to provide your personal data to us, then you have consented in an informed way to the processing of those data for the purposes indicated in this policy. 

**Closing the account**

You may remove/close your account at all times.  In such a case your profile will be removed and your personal data will no longer be processed. As regards other members, the content of your account disappears and all your personal  data, except the content that had been processed by other lawful users through reactions and the like. ** **

**Notification of the Privacy Protection Commission**

The processing of personal data by Limebooth is reported to the Privacy Protection Commission, Rue Haute 139 Hoogstraat, 1000 Brussels, Belgium, [www.privacy.fgov.be](http://www.privacy.fgov.be/).

**Changes to the privacy policy**

This privacy policy is subject to possible change in the future.  The amended privacy policy shall be posted on the Limebooth website and shall enter into force automatically thirty days after the initial posting on the site.  Although Limebooth will try to publicise any change, you are nonetheless advised to go over these terms and conditions periodically.
